(sighs)
(Leonard:)Should we call Sheldon
and Howard?
(Raj:)No. We can do this by ourselves.
(Leonard:)Okay. Great.
How do you want to start?
(Raj:)I don't know.
Sheldon. Sheldon.
(Howard:)Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)I bet that started off
as a joke,
(Sheldon:)but by the third one
you realized
(Sheldon:)there was something
strangely enjoyable about it.
(Penny:)Yeah, I kind of want
to do it again.
(Sheldon:)I don't recommend it. You'll be
doing it the rest of your life.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, if you're looking for
Leonard, he's with Koothrappali.
(Penny:)Uh, no, I actually came
to talk to you.
(Sheldon:)How nice.
(Sheldon:)Here are some topics
that interest me:
(Sheldon:)quantum mechanics,
trains, flags...
No, no.
(Penny:)It's about my acting career.
Oh, sorry.
(Sheldon:)That's not on the list.
(Howard:)Well...
Oh, wait. No.